==== START ====
ignition 0
ignition 1
fans running
ignition 2
electricity runs in
train starts
maltiyskiy cross
train going forward
train side view
==== TRANSFORMER ====
arrow
coils
primary on
secondary show
secondary on
arrow
arrow 2
two secondaries
split secondaries
highlight secondaries
==== ROTATE TRANSFORMER ====
highlight primary
highlight secondary
25000 volts
secondary sequence
arrow towards movement
current flow
==== CONTACTOR SWITCH ====
next switch
air valve
contactor switch
big contactor sequence
==== BIG CONTACTOR SCHEMATIC ====
contactor coil start change
arrow
sw off
sw on
arrow
sw off
sw on
==== TRAIN MAN ====
clock
train
==== IGNITRONS ====
electrode
arrow
arrow 2
PTYTb
ignitron scene
cathode spot
aux electrode
main electrode
current stop
phase 2
phase 3
phase 4
2 ignitrons graph
second sinus
liquid anode
anode current
triple inductor
big ignitron schematic
+ motors
motors scene
waveform
arrows on shunts
full schematic
motor teardown
motor coil
coil interconnects
motor man
motor man rotate the handle
rotate 2
rotate 3
==== TRANSFORMER COOL ====
starts cooling
ignitron cooling
ignitron stage
25 celsium
heater
thermostat scene
35 celsium
38 celsium valve open
control valve
arrow
arrow 2
switch off valve
red signal lamp
==== MAINS SWITCH ====
arrow
start valve run
main valve air
circuit breaker scene
arrows
arc blowing
arc jump
arrow
air drive
breaker movement
arrow
arrow 2
arrow 3