==== START ====
ignition 1
ignition 2
maltiyskiy cross
==== TRANSFORMER ====
primary on
secondary on
==== ROTATE TRANSFORMER ====
secondary seq 1
arrow towards movement
==== CONTACTOR SWITCH ====
air valve
==== BIG CONTACTOR SCHEMATIC ====
contactor coil start change
arrow
sw off
sw on
arrow
sw off
sw on
==== TRAIN MAN ====
clock
train
==== IGNITRONS ====
electrode
ignitron scene
cathode spot
aux electrode
main electrode
current stop
phase 2
phase 3
phase 4
2 ignitrons graph
second sinus
liquid anode
anode current
triple inductor
big ignitron schematic
+ motors
motors scene
waveform
full schematic
motor teardown
motor coil
coil interconnects
motor man
motor man rotate the handle
rotate 2
rotate 3
==== TRANSFORMER COOL ====
starts cooling
ignitron cooling
ignitron stage
heater
thermostat scene
38 celsium valve open
control valve
red signal lamp
==== MAINS SWITCH ====
switch 1
air breaker open
switch air valve movement
overcurrent break
switch by hand
start the current
relay off with arrow
failure current go
train main rotate the shturval
switch on
big arrow and relay off
current starts
sw on relay
backcurrent relay off
THUNDER
rotating motor
koda
film end
end of file